Peace, what's going on? Nasirr with another INNERG
frequency, INNERG INTEL. I hope you guys
have been tapping in with some of the
latest videos, making sure you get any
information on AI, no, focusing on your
finances. And if you haven't tapped in on
Legacy In Ink: The Final Frequency is
now available. Please go support that. My
second book. All young men and young
sisters, tap in with this book so you can
get on a frequency that raises your
awareness, your consciousness, your
habits, your overall well-being. Alright,
I'll put all that information in the
description. We're also on the road to a
thousand subs, so if you ain't subscribed
to the energy, please drop a sub, drop a
like on these videos. That means a lot. It
helps me keep going. It helps me keep
putting out these videos, taking the time
out to share the information and gain with
you guys. For those that are interested in
any of the things that I talk about, want
to talk about it more, want to get some
one-on-ones, get some teachings classes. I
will be hosting a class soon, so
definitely keep tapping. I tried to do a
class earlier this year, but it didn't
work out. So, I appreciate you guys for
still tapping in and supporting. So, if
you guys want that, I'll be putting out
more information within the next couple of
weeks on that class in regards to agents
and learning fundamentals on those tools.
This video, however, will be focused on
investing crypto in this next bull run. If
you don't know what a bull run is, it is
essentially when coins, stocks, assets go
up. Simple. The bull run means you need to
be in it before it runs up because once it
goes up, it's up. So, right now, this
frequency will be market cycles,
discussing how is it similar to the 2020
market cycle bull run. I'll be explaining
some tokenizations, some stable coins. At
the beginning, I will be explaining how
you have $10, $25, or even $50. You don't
need $100. You don't need $1,000 to start
investing. You see, and you got
diversifications in these portfolios,
mistakes new investors can make and things
that they should avoid. And then at the
end, if you stick around, I'll be sharing
my personal stocks, ETFs, my crypto watch
list that I'll be, you know, watching
months. I just want us to understand that
this is not financial advice, you know, to
see you guys on things that I found,
things that I've learned. And you know,
guys, to do your own research on it and
see if it resonates in where you can fit
in. I mean, if it's good, if not, you
know, there's other things to invest in
and assets that you can focus on, right?
But if you want to get in a crypto
blockchain technology and you see
something happening on the horizon, you
know, you want to go to that. All right,
don't forget that. Hit that sub button and
I'll see y'all on the other side. Peace.
Peace.
How's it going on? So I want to start off
by giving you a visual of, you know, the
2020 bull run. I mean, where are we
currently at 2026 right.
So visual people, this is pretty much
where we are at right here. Right.
Compared to 2020. And if you know anything
about bull market cycles or bull runs, if
not finished watching this video, I'm
explain, you know, topics and terms that
you should know. But for those that do
know, this is my, my, my basis for why I
am seeing what I'm seeing and why I am,
you know, supporting my thesis on the bull
market is starting. You want to get in
right now and this is the right time to
get the maximum gains, right? Again,
please like, subscribe, share to the video
to the YouTube channel. We're on the road
to 1000 subs. So if you do find
information value in this video, you know,
drop a sub, like share with friends,
family. And I'm going to dive into a whole
wide range of topics and things you should
be, you know, worried about and focused
on. Hit it into this end of the year going
into the new year. Alright, so just take a
look at this. Right here. The bull run,
right. The bull run cycle is going to just
rise up just like here in 2020. And it
just kept rising up, kept rising up
pullback rows of new house. You know, all
time house has been making a thing this
year. So when you see all time highs back
to back, that's a good sign, which means
it's a bull run indicator.